Neha Erasmus African Union High Level Implementation Panel Papers MS207
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Negotiations records, 2010 -- 2013; MS207.002; 911 Digital Object(s)
  - June 2011 negotiations, 2010 -- 2011; MS207.002.00058
    - Final Round Strategy Plan, 2011-06-06; MS207.002.00095
    - Outcomes from Internal AUHIP Meeting, 2011-06-07; MS207.002.00096
    - Final Negotiations Max Budget, 2011-06-09; MS207.002.00097
    - Final Negotiations Tentative calendar, 2011-06-09; MS207.002.00098
    - Draft Agenda for Interlinked Negotiations, 2011-06-11; MS207.002.00099
    - Final Negotiations Room Numbers, 2011-06-11; MS207.002.00100
    - Final Negotiations Room Numbers, 2011-06-11; MS207.002.00101
    - AUHIP Invitation Final Negotiations NCP, 2011-06-12; MS207.002.00102
    - AUHIP Invitation Final Negotiations SPLM, 2011-06-12; MS207.002.00103
    - Delegations List 13 June, 2011-06-13; MS207.002.00104
    - Letter Presidential Summit Catering, 2011-06-20; MS207.002.00105
    - Letter Presidential Summit Catering, 2011-06-20; MS207.002.00106
    - Letter Extension for Sudan Negotiations, 2011-06-23; MS207.002.00107
    - Draft 26 - 28 July 2011: Intensive Negotiations Schedule, 2011-06-25; MS207.002.00108
    - Draft Schedule for Sudan Negotiations, 26 - 28 June, 2011-06-25; MS207.002.00109
    - Roadmap, 2011-06-27; MS207.002.00110
    - AUHIP report 3 July 2011, 2011-07-03; MS207.002.00111
    - AUHIP report 3 July 2011, 2011-07-03; MS207.002.00112
    - Final Negotiations Participant List, 2011-12-21; MS207.002.00113
    - June/July 2011 Participant List, 2011-12-21; MS207.002.00114
  - July 2011 negotiations, MS207.002.00115
    - Economic negotiations, 2011; MS207.002.00116
      - Summary of Conference Call Econ Team, 2011-07-15; MS207.002.00117
      - Memo on The Sudans: Currency Issues, 2011-07-17; MS207.002.00118
      - Draft points of agreement on currency-related issues for an interim arrangement, 2011-07-28; MS207.002.00119
      - Econ Agreement - Finance, Economic and Natural Resource Cluster, 2011-07-29; MS207.002.00120
      - Negotiations between Sudan and South Sudan on interim economic arrangements: Points Agreed, 2011-07-29; MS207.002.00121
      - Macroeconomic impact of the Loss of Oil Revenues, 2011-08-02; MS207.002.00122
    - Prepatory documents, 2011; MS207.002.00123
      - Negotiations Budget, 2011-06-09; MS207.002.00124
      - NCP Delegation, 2011-07-03; MS207.002.00125
      - Security Council Resolution 1996 (2011), 2011-07-08; MS207.002.00126
      - SAF Delegation, 2011-07-25; MS207.002.00127
      - Econ Security Negotiations Participants List, 2011-07-27; MS207.002.00128
      - Flight Details Econ Sec Delegation, 2011-07-27; MS207.002.00129
      - Participant List, 2011-07-27; MS207.002.00130
      - 28 July Negotiations Participants, 2011-07-28; MS207.002.00131
    - Security documents, 2011; MS207.002.00132
      - Joint Position Paper on Operationalisation of Border Security and the Joint Political and Security Mechanism - v. 11, 2011-06-24; MS207.002.00133
      - Joint Position Paper on Operationalisation of Border Security and the Joint Political and Security Mechanism - v. 11, 2011-06-24; MS207.002.00134
      - Joint Position Paper on Operationalisation of Border Security and the Joint Political and Security Mechanism - v. 12, 2011-06-28; MS207.002.00135
      - Agreement on Operationalisation of Border Security and the Joint Political and Security Mechanism, 2011-07-03; MS207.002.00136
      - JPSM prep meeting agenda, 2011-07-13; MS207.002.00137
      - JPSM prep meeting agenda - SAF suggestions, 2011-07-18; MS207.002.00138
      - JPSM and JC meeting agenda, 2011-07-21; MS207.002.00139
      - Draft Joint Position Paper, 2011-07-28; MS207.002.00140
      - Tasks of the Third Party, 2011-07-28; MS207.002.00141
      - Tasks, 2011-07-28; MS207.002.00142
      - Annex A Third Party Tasks, 2011-07-29; MS207.002.00143
      - Annex B Rules of Procedure, 2011-07-29; MS207.002.00144
      - Border Security Agreement - v2, 2011-07-29; MS207.002.00145
      - Border Security Agreement - v1, 2011-07-29; MS207.002.00146
      - Security Minutes, 2011-07-29; MS207.002.00147
      - Annex B Tasks JBVMS - JBVMT, 2011-07-30; MS207.002.00148
      - Annex C Rules of Procedure, 2011-07-30; MS207.002.00149
      - AUHIP Proposals for Paragraphs - v1, 2011-07-30; MS207.002.00150
      - AUHIP Proposals for Paragraphs - v2, 2011-07-30; MS207.002.00151
      - AUHIP Proposals for Paragraphs - v3, 2011-07-30; MS207.002.00152
      - AUHIP Proposals for Paragraphs - v4, 2011-07-30; MS207.002.00153
      - AUHIP Proposals for Paragraphs - v5, 2011-07-30; MS207.002.00154
      - AUHIP Proposals for Paragraphs - v6, 2011-07-30; MS207.002.00155
      - AUHIP Proposals for Paragraphs - v8, 2011-07-30; MS207.002.00156
      - AUHIP Proposals for Paragraphs - v9, 2011-07-30; MS207.002.00157
      - Border Security Agreement - v3, 2011-07-30; MS207.002.00158
      - Border Security Agreement - v4, 2011-07-30; MS207.002.00159
      - AUHIP Letter to UNSG, 2011-07-30; MS207.002.00160
      - Security Agreement, 2011-07-30; MS207.002.00161
      - AUHIP letter Luckham, 2011-08-01; MS207.002.00162
  - September 2011 negotiations, MS207.002.00163
    - Accommodation List, 2011-08-09; MS207.002.00164
    - Negotiations Budget, 2011-08-28; MS207.002.00165
    - Delegation List 6 September 2011, 2011-09-06; MS207.002.00166
  - October 2011 negotiations, MS207.002.00167
    - AUHIP Update for Partners, 2011-10-04; MS207.002.00168
    - AUHIP Update for Team, 2011-10-04; MS207.002.00169
    - Negotiations Budget, 2011-10-06; MS207.002.00170
  - November 2011 negotiations, 2011 -- 2012; MS207.002.00171
    - AUHIP Draft Programme Nov, 2011-10-30; MS207.002.00172
    - Proposed Strategy on Transitional Financial Arrangements, 2011-10-30; MS207.002.00173
    - "TFA+" Proposal Skeleton, 2011-10-30; MS207.002.00174
    - Guidance from the Panel, 2011-10-31; MS207.002.00175
    - Reflections on the Strategy, 2011-10-31; MS207.002.00176; Afako, Barney
    - Reflections on the Strategy, 2011-10-31; MS207.002.00177; Afako, Barney
    - AUHIP Negotiations Programme November, 2011-11-04; MS207.002.00178
    - AUHIP 3 Track Strategy Parties, 2011-11-08; MS207.002.00179
    - AUHIP 3 Track Strategy Parties, 2011-11-08; MS207.002.00180
    - Draft AUHIP Programme, 2011-11-08; MS207.002.00181
    - AUHIP Programme November Internal, 2011-11-11; MS207.002.00182
    - AUHIP Programme November Logistics, 2011-11-11; MS207.002.00183
    - Accommodation List 141111, 2011-11-14; MS207.002.00184
    - AUHIP Programme November External, 2011-11-14; MS207.002.00185
    - AUHIP Programme November Internal, 2011-11-14; MS207.002.00186
    - Proposal on Transitional Financial Arrangements and Some Other Matters - Final, 2011-11-14; MS207.002.00187
    - Proposal on Transitional Financial Arrangements and Some Other Matters - Final, 2011-11-14; MS207.002.00188
    - Checklist, 2011-11-14; MS207.002.00189
    - Sudan Accommodation Hilton, 2011-11-27; MS207.002.00190
    - Sudan/South Sudan Accommodation, 2011-11-28; MS207.002.00191
    - Government of Sudan's Response to Republic of South Sudan Presentation - Oil/Transportation fees, 2011-11-29; MS207.002.00192
    - AUHIP Programme November, 2011-11-29; MS207.002.00193
    - PSC Communique Sudan, 2011-11-30; MS207.002.00194
    - Accommodation.List, 2011-11-26; MS207.002.00195
    - Proposed Programme Dec/Jan, 2012-01-12; MS207.002.00196
  - December 2011 negotiations, MS207.002.00197
    - Attachments, 2011; MS207.002.00198
      - GoRSS letter to AUHIP Arrears, 2011-12-12; MS207.002.00199
      - GoRSS letter to AUHIP Arrears Appendix, 2011-12-12; MS207.002.00200
      - GoRSS letter to GoS Arrears - Appendix Draft Pensions, 2011-12-12; MS207.002.00201
      - GoRSS letter to GoS Arrears, 2011-12-12; MS207.002.00202
      - GoRSS letter to AUHIP oil companies, 2011-12-13; MS207.002.00203
      - GoRSS letter to AUHIP Sequencing, 2011-12-13; MS207.002.00204
    - Excerpt from AUHIP TFA Proposal on Arrears, 2011-12-07; MS207.002.00205
    - Brief on Oil Negotiations - Planning the Next AUHIP Sudan/ South Sudan Meeting, 2011-12-18; MS207.002.00206
    - Outcome December Meeting - AUHIP Proposal: Agenda and Process for January Meetings, 2011-12-20; MS207.002.00207
    - PB Letter to Chairman, 2011-12-21; MS207.002.00208
    - PB Summary, 2011-12-21; MS207.002.00209
  - January 2012 negotiations, 2011 -- 2012; MS207.002.00210
    - Proposals, 2012; MS207.002.00211
      - AUHIP Cover Agreement, 2012-01-24; MS207.002.00212
      - AUHIP Terms of Agreement - final markup, 2012-01-24; MS207.002.00213
      - AUHIP Terms of Agreement - final, 2012-01-24; MS207.002.00214
    - Accommodation Sudan Negotiations, 2011-02-12; MS207.002.00215
    - Draft Schedule of Negotiations and Related Meetings, 2012-01-06; MS207.002.00216
    - AUHIP Draft Invitation letter, 2012-01-11; MS207.002.00217
    - AUHIP Invitation letter, 2012-01-11; MS207.002.00218
    - AUHIP Invitation letter GoRSS, 2012-01-11; MS207.002.00219
    - AUHIP Invitation letter GoRSS, 2012-01-11; MS207.002.00220
    - AUHIP Invitation letter GoS, 2012-01-11; MS207.002.00221
    - AUHIP visa letter FOCs Khartoum, 2012-01-12; MS207.002.00222
    - Conferencing final, 2012-01-12; MS207.002.00223
    - Accommodation Sudan Negotiations, 2012-01-14; MS207.002.00224
    - AUHIP Invitation FOCs, 2012-01-15; MS207.002.00225
    - AUHIP Invitation FOCs, 2012-01-15; MS207.002.00226
    - AUHIP Invite Nationality GoRSS, 2012-01-15; MS207.002.00227
    - AUHIP Invite Nationality GoRSS, 2012-01-15; MS207.002.00228
    - AUHIP Invite Nationality GoS, 2012-01-15; MS207.002.00229
    - AUHIP Invite Nationality GoS, 2012-01-15; MS207.002.00230
    - AUHIP visa letter FOCs Juba, 2012-01-15; MS207.002.00231
    - AUHIP visa letter FOCs Juba, 2012-01-15; MS207.002.00232
    - AUHIP visa letter FOCs Khartoum, 2012-01-15; MS207.002.00233
    - Conferencing, 2012-01-16; MS207.002.00234
    - Conferencing option 2, 2012-01-16; MS207.002.00235
    - Conferencing option 3, 2012-01-16; MS207.002.00236
    - AUHIP letter JPSM GoS, 2012-01-17; MS207.002.00237
    - AUHIP letter JPSM GoS GoRSS, 2012-01-17; MS207.002.00238
    - Simple Proposal for Interim and Permanent Arrangements on Oil, 2012-01-17; MS207.002.00239
    - Abdul Mohammed Request for Negotiations Funding, 2012-01-18; MS207.002.00240
    - Presentation for Addis Ababa Negotiation Meeting - Integrated version v4 18.1.2012 presented, 2012-01-18; MS207.002.00241; Greater Nile Petroleum Operating Company Limited
    - Presentatation on Transportation System for Africa union (final), 2012-01-18; MS207.002.00242; Petrodar Operating Co.
    - AUHIP visa letter JOCs Juba, 2012-09-12; MS207.002.00243
    - AUHIP visa letter JOCs Juba, 2012-09-13; MS207.002.00244
  - February 2012 negotiations, MS207.002.00245
    - Joint Political Security Mechanism, 2012; MS207.002.00246
      - Record of Decision, 2012-02-10; MS207.002.00247
      - Partial Minutes, 2012-02-11; MS207.002.00248; Erasmus, Neha
    - AUHIP Agenda letter GoRSS, 2012-02-03; MS207.002.00249
    - AUHIP Invitation letter GoRSS, 2012-02-03; MS207.002.00250
    - AUHIP Invitation letter GoRSS, 2012-02-03; MS207.002.00251
    - AUHIP Invitation letter GoS, 2012-02-03; MS207.002.00252
    - AUHIP Invitation letter GoS, 2012-02-03; MS207.002.00253
    - AUHIP letter JPSM GoRSS, 2012-02-03; MS207.002.00254
    - AUHIP letter JPSM GoRSS, 2012-02-03; MS207.002.00255
    - AUHIP letter JPSM GoS, 2012-02-03; MS207.002.00256
    - AUHIP letter JPSM GoS, 2012-02-03; MS207.002.00257
    - AUHIP Invitation FOCs, 2012-02-05; MS207.002.00258
    - AUHIP Invitation FOCs, 2012-02-05; MS207.002.00259
    - AUHIP Letter JPSM UNISFA, 2012-02-05; MS207.002.00260
    - AUHIP Letter JPSM UNISFA, 2012-02-05; MS207.002.00261
    - Feb Negotiations Conferencing, 2012-02-06; MS207.002.00262
    - AUHIP visa letter Petronas, 2012-02-07; MS207.002.00263
    - AUHIP visa letter Petronas, 2012-02-07; MS207.002.00264
    - Update for Negotiations, 2012-02-08; MS207.002.00265
    - Update for Negotiations, 2012-02-08; MS207.002.00266
    - Abdul Mohammed Request Feb Negotiations Norway, 2012-02-09; MS207.002.00267
    - Schedule of Meetings for February Negotiations, 2012-02-09; MS207.002.00268
    - Programme, 2012-02-10; MS207.002.00269
    - Abdul Mohammed letter Borders Reps GoRSS, 2012-02-11; MS207.002.00270
    - Abdul Mohammed letter Borders Reps GoRSS, 2012-02-11; MS207.002.00271
    - Abdul Mohammed letter Borders Reps GoS, 2012-02-11; MS207.002.00272
    - Abdul Mohammed letter Borders Reps GoS, 2012-02-11; MS207.002.00273
    - AUHIP Agenda letter GoS, 2012-02-12; MS207.002.00274
    - AUHIP request Tran Agreement GoRSS, 2012-02-13; MS207.002.00275
    - AUHIP Press Release on the Nationality Review Meeting, 2012-02-15; MS207.002.00276
    - Abdul Mohammed Request March Negotiations IGAD, 2012-02-21; MS207.002.00277
    - Abdul Mohammed Request March Negotiations IGAD, 2012-02-21; MS207.002.00278
    - AUHIP letter JPSM GoS, 2012-04-09; MS207.002.00279
  - March 2012 negotiations, 2012 -- 2013; MS207.002.00280
    - Draft Non-Paper: Background Note for High-Level 3+3 Negotiations on Oil and Related Issues, 2012-02-16; MS207.002.00281
    - AUHIP Non-Paper: Background Note for High-Level 3+3 Negotiations on Oil and Related Issues - Draft, 2012-02-23; MS207.002.00282
    - AUHIP Non-Paper: Background Note for High-Level 3+3 Negotiations on Oil and Related Issues, 2012-02-23; MS207.002.00283
    - AUHIP Invitation letter GoRSS, 2012-02-25; MS207.002.00284
    - AUHIP Invitation letter GoRSS, 2012-02-27; MS207.002.00285
    - AUHIP Invitation letter GoS, 2012-02-27; MS207.002.00286
    - Brief Update on Dynamics in Khartoum, 2012-02-27; MS207.002.00287
    - Prospects for the Two Sudans, 2012-03-04; MS207.002.00288
    - Suggested AUHIP Timeline, 2012-03-12; MS207.002.00289
    - Suggested Strategy and Timeline, 2012-03-13; MS207.002.00290
    - Suggested Strategy and Timeline, 2012-03-13; MS207.002.00291
    - Suggested Strategy and Timeline, 2012-03-15; MS207.002.00292
    - AUHIP letter 2A Postponement SPLMN, 2013-03-14; MS207.002.00293
  - April 2012 negotiations, MS207.002.00294
    - Invitations, 2012; MS207.002.00295
      - AUHIP Invite Nationality Borders GoRSS, 2012-03-22; MS207.002.00296
      - AUHIP Invite Nationality Borders GoRSS, 2012-03-22; MS207.002.00297
      - AUHIP Invite Nationality Borders GoS, 2012-03-22; MS207.002.00298
      - AUHIP Invite Nationality Borders GoS, 2012-03-22; MS207.002.00299
      - AUHIP letter Government of the Republic of South Sudan - JPSM, 2012-03-22; MS207.002.00300
      - AUHIP letter Government of the Republic of South Sudan - JPSM, 2012-03-22; MS207.002.00301
      - AUHIP letter Government of Sudan - AJOC, 2012-03-22; MS207.002.00302
      - AUHIP letter Government of the Republic of South Sudan - JPSM, 2012-03-22; MS207.002.00303
      - AUHIP letter Government of the Republic of South Sudan - JPSM, 2012-03-22; MS207.002.00304
      - AUHIP letter Government of Sudan - JPSM, 2012-03-22; MS207.002.00305
      - AUHIP letter Government of Sudan - JPSM, 2012-03-22; MS207.002.00306
      - AUHIP Proposed Agenda for Meeting of the Implementation of the Framework Agreement on the Status of Nationals of the Other State and Related Matters, 2012-03-22; MS207.002.00307
    - AUHIP Invitation, 2012-03-16; MS207.002.00308
    - AUHIP draft letter to UNSC, 2012-03-17; MS207.002.00309
    - AUHIP Letter to Bashir - Summit - Draft 3, 2012-03-18; MS207.002.00310
    - AUHIP Letter to President Salva Kiir Mayardit - Summit - Draft 3, 2012-03-18; MS207.002.00311
    - Abdul Mohammed Request Negotiations IGAD, 2012-03-22; MS207.002.00312
    - Abdul Mohammed Request Negotiations IGAD, 2012-03-22; MS207.002.00313
    - AUHIP Letter to Bashir - Summit, 2012-03-23; MS207.002.00314
    - AUHIP Letter to President Salva Kiir Mayardit - Summit, 2012-03-23; MS207.002.00315
    - Confidential Update on Developments in Preparation for the Presidential Summit, 2012-03-25; MS207.002.00316
    - Two Sudans summit narrative agenda, 2012-03-25; MS207.002.00317
    - Two Sudans Summit statement, 2012-03-25; MS207.002.00318
    - AUC Border tension press release, 2012-03-27; MS207.002.00319
    - AUC Border tension press release, 2012-03-27; MS207.002.00320
    - Two Areas Brainstorming Meeting 3 April 2012, 2012-04-03; MS207.002.00321
    - Draft Request UNMISS aircraft, 2012-04-04; MS207.002.00322
    - JPSM joint decisions d3, 2012-04-04; MS207.002.00323
    - JPSM joint decisions d5, 2012-04-09; MS207.002.00324
  - May 2012 negotiations, MS207.002.00325
    - Briefings and Staff preparation, 2012; MS207.002.00326
      - Memorandum - Issues Concerning the Security Map, 2012-05-10; MS207.002.00327
      - Security Talks: "Make Haste Slowly" - Preparation, Preparation, Preparation!, 2012-05-13; MS207.002.00328
      - Security Brief, 2012-05-16; MS207.002.00329
      - Security Brief and Response to Thabo Mbeki Queries, 2012-05-17; MS207.002.00330
      - Security Brief and Response to Thabo Mbeki Queries - Draft 2, 2012-05-17; MS207.002.00331
      - Staff and Partners Meeting Agenda d2, 2012-05-28; MS207.002.00332
      - Staff and Partners Meeting Agenda d3, 2012-05-28; MS207.002.00333
      - Staff and Partners Meeting Agenda d4, 2012-05-28; MS207.002.00334
    - Correspondence, 2012; MS207.002.00335
      - AUHIP letter Malike Agar, 2012-06-06; MS207.002.00336
      - AUHIP letter Malike Agar, 2012-06-06; MS207.002.00337
      - AUHIP letter Map SK, 2012-06-06; MS207.002.00338
      - AUHIP letter Abyei SK, 2012-06-07; MS207.002.00339
    - Invitations, 2012; MS207.002.00340
      - AUHIP invite JPSM Government of Sudan, 2012-02-03; MS207.002.00341
      - AUHIP LNP Invite Government of South Sudan, 2012-05-22; MS207.002.00342
      - AUHIP LNP Invite Government of South Sudan, 2012-05-22; MS207.002.00343
      - AUHIP LNP Invite Government of Sudan, 2012-05-22; MS207.002.00344
      - AUHIP LNP Invite Government of Sudan, 2012-05-22; MS207.002.00345
      - AUHIP LNP Invite Special Envoys, 2012-05-23; MS207.002.00346
      - AUHIP LNP Invite Endre Stiansen/Norway, 2012-05-23; MS207.002.00347
      - AUHIP LNP Invite Tesfaye Tadesse/UNISFA, 2012-05-23; MS207.002.00348
      - AUHIP LNP Invite Haile Menkerios/UN, 2012-05-23; MS207.002.00349
      - AUHIP LNP Invite Liu Guijin/China, 2012-05-23; MS207.002.00350
      - AUHIP LNP Invite Mikhail Margelov/Russia, 2012-05-23; MS207.002.00351
      - AUHIP LNP Invite Princeton Lyman/USA, 2012-05-23; MS207.002.00352
      - AUHIP LNP Invite Robin Gwynn/UK, 2012-05-23; MS207.002.00353
      - AUHIP LNP Invite Robin Gwynn/UK, 2012-05-23; MS207.002.00354
      - AUHIP LNP Invite Rosalind Marsden/EU, 2012-05-23; MS207.002.00355
      - AUHIP LNP Invite Salah Halima/League of Arab States, 2012-05-23; MS207.002.00356
      - AUHIP Invite JPSM Government of South Sudan, 2012-06-01; MS207.002.00357
      - AUHIP Invite JPSM Government of South Sudan, 2012-06-01; MS207.002.00358
      - AUHIP invite JPSM Government of Sudan, 2012-06-01; MS207.002.00359
      - AUHIP invite JPSM Government of Sudan, 2012-06-01; MS207.002.00360
    - Joint Political Security Mechanism, 2012; MS207.002.00361
      - Prepatory Committee, 2012; MS207.002.00362
        - JPSM PrepCom narrative agenda d2, 2012-05-02; MS207.002.00363
        - JPSM Agenda Table d1, 2012-06-02; MS207.002.00364
      - RSS Compliance letter matrix and all annexes, 2012; MS207.002.00365
        - Cover Letter from RSS to Mbeki re UNSC Res 2046 compliance, 2012-06-04; MS207.002.00366
        - Annex A - Lt.Gen. John Kong Nyuon to Thabo Mbeki, 2012-04-04; MS207.002.00367
        - Annex B - Letter from Emmanuel LoWilla/Republic of South Sudan to Jean Ping/Chairperson African Union, 2012-04-27; MS207.002.00368
        - Annex C - Letter from Emmanuel LoWilla/Republic of South Sudan, 2012-04-30; MS207.002.00369
        - Annex D - Letter from Emmanuel LoWilla/Republic of South Sudan to Jean Ping/Chairperson African Union - p. 1, 2012-05-03; MS207.002.00370
        - Annex D - Letter from Emmanuel LoWilla/Republic of South Sudan to Jean Ping/Chairperson African Union - p. 2, 2012-05-03; MS207.002.00371
        - Annex E - Letter from Emmanuel LoWilla/Republic of South Sudan to Agshin Mehdiyev/President of the UN Security Council - p. 1, 2012-05-03; MS207.002.00372
        - Annex E - Letter from Emmanuel LoWilla/Republic of South Sudan to Agshin Mehdiyev/President of the UN Security Council - p. 2, 2012-05-03; MS207.002.00373
        - Annex F - Letter from Orifa Oswaha/Permanent Mission of South Sudan to the UN to Susan E. Rice/President of UN Security Council, 2012-04-28; MS207.002.00374
        - Annex G - South Sudan police withdraw from disputed Abyei: U.N., 2012-05-11; MS207.002.00375
          Abyei (Sudan); Media, Mass; Police; Boundary disputes
        - Annex H - Letter from Pagan Amum to Deng Alor - p. 1, 2012-05-24; MS207.002.00376
        - Annex H - Letter from Pagan Amum to Deng Alor - p. 2, 2012-05-24; MS207.002.00377
        - Annex I - The African Union Welcomes the Withdrawel of the South Sudan Police Forces from Abyei, 2012-05-11; MS207.002.00378
          Abyei (Sudan); Boundary disputes; Police; African Union. Peace and Security Council; African Union
        - Annex J - Presidential Order No.17/2012 (Republic of South Sudan) for the Formation of a Joint High Level Committee on Nationals - p. 1, 2012-05-24; MS207.002.00379
        - Annex J - Presidential Order No.17/2012 (Republic of South Sudan) for the Formation of a Joint High Level Committee on Nationals - p. 3, 2012-05-24; MS207.002.00380
        - Annex J - Presidential Order No.17/2012 (Republic of South Sudan) for the Formation of a Joint High Level Committee on Nationals - p.2, 2012-05-24; MS207.002.00381
        - Annex K - Internal Rules of Procedure Joint High Level Commission March 2012, 2012-03; MS207.002.00382
        - Annex K - Letter from Pagan to Mbeki - upcoming talks in Addis, 2012-03-28; MS207.002.00383
        - Annex L - Decree 1, 2012-05-24; MS207.002.00384
        - Annex L - Decree 2, 2012-05-24; MS207.002.00385
        - Annex M - Presidential Order - Form JBC2, 2012-03-14; MS207.002.00386
        - Annex M - Presidential Order - Formation of JBC, 2012-03-14; MS207.002.00387
        - Annex N - Aide Memoire, 2012-03-18; MS207.002.00388
        - Annex O - all Bombing before 24 April 2012, 2012-04-24; MS207.002.00389
        - Annex O - all Bombing before 24 April 2012, 2012-04-24; MS207.002.00390
        - Annex O - Letter from Franzis Nazaria/Permanent Mission of the Republic of South Sudan to the UN to Agshin Mehdiyev/President of the UN Security Council - p. 1, 2012-05-30; MS207.002.00391
        - Annex O - Letter from Franzis Nazaria/Permanent Mission of the Republic of South Sudan to the UN to Agshin Mehdiyev/President of the UN Security Council - p. 2, 2012-05-30; MS207.002.00392
        - Annex O - Letter from Franzis Nazaria/Permanent Mission of the Republic of South Sudan to the UN to Agshin Mehdiyev/President of the UN Security Council - p. 3, 2012-05-30; MS207.002.00393
        - Annex O - Letter from Franzis Nazaria/Permanent Mission of the Republic of South Sudan to the UN to Agshin Mehdiyev/President of the UN Security Council - p. 4, 2012-05-30; MS207.002.00394
        - Annex P - South Sudan/Pillaw Bor Wrap, 2012-05-11; MS207.002.00395
        - Annex Q - Bashir threatens to spurn UNSC resolution on Sudan, 2012-05-11; MS207.002.00396
        - Annex R - NCP Says Security Issues Prerequisite to Negotiations with South Sudan, 2012-06-03; MS207.002.00397
      - Safe Demilitarized Border Zone Map, 2012; MS207.002.00398
        - AUHIP SDBZ Map, 2012-06-01; MS207.002.00399